you're so selfish  啊
你真自私啊
what an idiot
真是个白痴
it's not my fault we're always late  forget it
我们总是迟到不是我的错，算了吧。
criticism  contempt
批评蔑视
defensiveness
防御性
and stonewalling  Dr
并阻挠博士
John Gottman calls these negative communication
约翰·戈特曼称这些负面沟通
patterns the four horsemen of the apocalypse
天启四骑士的模式
because they'll lead to the end of your relationship
因为它们会导致你们关系的终结
in fact  he can predict this relationship failure with over
事实上，他可以预测这段关系的失败
ninety percent accuracy if the behavior isn't changed
如果行为没有改变，90%的准确率
oh no
噢不
so  what can you do  well
那你能做好什么？
at the Gottman institute
在戈特曼学院
we understand you might not even know
我们知道你可能不知道
you're communicating this way
你是这样交流的
or you might not know how to control it
或者你可能不知道如何控制它
but if you practice the following
但是如果你练习以下内容
four research based antidotes
四种基于研究的解毒剂
there is hope for your future
你的未来还有希望
criticism attacks the character of the recipient
批评攻击接受者的品格
instead of focusing on a specific behavior
而不是专注于特定的行为
the antidote to criticism is to talk
批评的解药是谈话
about your feelings using i statements
用我的陈述来表达你的感受
then express a positive need
然后表达积极的需求
contempt is an expression of
蔑视是一种表达
superiority that comes out as sarcasm cynicism
以讽刺冷嘲热讽的方式出现的优越感
name calling eye rolling sneering
骂人翻白眼冷笑
mockery and hostile humor
嘲弄和敌意幽默
contempt is the greatest predictor of
蔑视是
relationship failure and must be eliminated
关系失败，必须消除
the antidote to contempt is to treat one
蔑视的解药是对待一个人
another with respect and build a culture of
另一个尊重并建立一种文化
appreciation within the relationship
关系中的欣赏
defensiveness is self protection through
防御是通过自我保护
righteous indignation or playing the victim
义愤填膺还是扮演受害者
defensiveness never solves the problem
防御性永远解决不了问题
and is really just an underhanded
真的只是一个卑鄙的人
way of blaming your partner
责怪你搭档的方式
the antidote to defensiveness is to accept responsibility
防御的解药是接受责任
even if only for part of the conflict
即使只是冲突的一部分
stonewalling occurs when the listener withdraws from
当听众退出时，就会发生阻挠
the conversation without resolving anything
没有解决任何问题的对话
it takes time for the negativity created by the
这需要时间来制造消极情绪
first three horsemen to result in stonewalling
前三个骑兵造成了阻碍
but when it does
但当它发生时
it can become a habit
它可以成为一种习惯
the antidote to stonewalling is to
阻挠的解毒剂是
break for at least twenty minutes  calm down
休息至少二十分钟冷静下来
then return to the conversation
然后回到对话
spared your relationship from certain destruction
让你们的关系免于毁灭
learn more about eliminating the four
了解有关消除四个的更多信息
horsemen by visiting our site
骑士通过访问我们的网站